const cards = [
    {question: "What is a group of penguins called?", answer : "A group of penguins in the water is called a raft but on land they're called a waddle!"},
    {question: "Why are some penguins black and white?", answer : "When swimming, the black on their backs helps them blend in with the darkness of the ocean from predators viewing from above. Their white bellies help them blend in with the bright surface of the ocean when viewed by predators and prey from below."},
    {question: "Why do penguins huddle together?", answer : "This behavior helps these birds protect themselves from predators. In frigid habitats, huddling helps penguins retain warmth."},
    {question: "Why do penguins have solid bones as opposed to the hollow bones of most birds?", answer : "Solid bones reduce buoyancy, but is also the reason they can't fly"},
    {question: "How do penguins stay warm?", answer : "In addition to feathers, they have a gland near the base of their tail to provide waterproof oil."},
    {question: "Where do penguins live?", answer : "You can find them in Antarctica and Antarctic islands, the Galapagos Islands off the coast of Ecuador, South Africa, New Zealand, Australia, Peru and Chile."},
    {question: "Would you ever see a penguin with a polar bear?", answer : "No!, That's because penguins live south of the equator while polar bears north of the equator in Arctic!"},
    {question: "How are penguin feet unique?", answer : "Penguin feet are adapted to help the birds steer while swimming. They use their feet like rudders, angling them to help control direction."},
    {question: "What do male penguins give females to win them over?", answer : "Rocks!"},
    {question: "How long have penguins been around? ", answer : "Fossils found in Antarctica suggest there were once giant penguins roaming the earth around 37 million years ago."},
];

export default cards;
